he is such an awesome man I just love
that guy okay let me uh bring
in Mr
Kaku
sorry hello hello how are you hi John
thank you for being able to be with us
oh I'm very happy to oh we still have uh
Dr Robert Duncan on he he he's has more
time but um Mr bny had to hang up ah I'm
sorry uh so I'm just gonna introduce you
really quick uh John kiraku you just
recently were released from prison after
serving was it 30 months uh 20 23 months
of a 30-month sentence okay um former
CIA analyst and case officer former
senior investigator for the Senate
Foreign Relations Committee former
counterterrorism consultant for ABC News
blogger for Huffington Post um the first
US government official to confirm in
December of 2007 under the Bush
Administration uh that water boarding
was being used to
interrogate uh people at not just iguano
but black sites all over the
world um on October 22nd of 2012 you
pleaded guilty to disclosing classified
information about a fellow CIA officer
that connected the covert operative to a
specific
operation uh he he were the first person
to pass classified information to a
reporter although the reporter did not
publish um the
information uh so right you were
sentence 30 months but served 23 out of
the 30 um and it was in Loretto
Pennsylvania correct so thank you for
being able to be on organic news here on
awake radio I'm very happy to be here
thanks for inviting me um I so yeah and
Dr Robert Duncan is um still with us so
yeah we were having a really good
conversation and so okay first how long
were you working for the
the CIA I was there for 14 and a half
years and and how how was your time
there I'll be honest with you I loved
the CIA I felt like I was really making
a contribution really making a
difference and I worked with some really
great people I worked with some
Psychopathic lunatics but most were
really great
people and and so right I mean like the
people were there they were really you
know interested in doing the right thing
and going
after right the yeah you know when when
I first got to the CIA I I kept my
politics to myself I I'm a lifelong
Progressive pretty pretty hardcore
Progressive and um and I kept it to
myself because I was afraid that um that
I wouldn't really fit in and it might
make it a little difficult to to get
along day today and the longer I was
there the more I realized that the is is
uh it's full of progressives just like
me uh you know I've always maintained
that the Republican party and the
conservative movement in in our country
do not have a monopoly on patriotism
Liberals are Patriots and I was I was
very proud to be there and for a long
time I felt like I was really doing
great work for an important cause and
then September 11th came and uh
everything everything changed what like
exactly like what was what would the
contrast
B
well I had switched to operations from
analysis in in
1998 and
um after the September 11th attacks we
began
opening secret sites and then torture
entered the Lexicon yeah and uh it just
it just wasn't the same it it was as
though it was as though so many so many
senior level and even mid senior CIA
officers had something to prove that
they could be tougher and meaner and
angrier than anybody else and it just
became an ugly Place yeah that's
unfortunate and
so it was in
2007 that you exposed water
boarding
as that was happening when it was
actually they they were completely lying
and saying that they were weren't using
torture
um they you know they you know that they
weren't doing you know any of this stuff
that's right the president actually came
right out and said we are not torturing
prisoners and I knew that that was a lie
right that see that that just cracks me
up that uh most Americans focus on
waterboarding they don't focus on shocks
or Burns and other physical beatings or
uh the them to be naked and perform
sexual acts and sexual Manner and duct
tape over the eyes and hypothermia and
Heat injury and mock executions and
threats to family I mean it goes on and
on they don't get Medicare the uh
medical service they don't have food or
water I mean it goes on the list of
tortures are like you know I have you
know four pages of torture techniques
they use but we focus on water boarding
and that's not even the worst of them
yes you're you're absolutely right I I
agree with that I I always thought that
there were even approved uh torture
techniques that were worse than water
boarding we know now that uh that sleep
deprivation actually caused some
prisoners to lose their minds and they
to uh participate in their own defenses
absolutely you got it correct there sir
and then the and then the cold cell
resulted in the death of one prisoner it
was so extreme yeah well oh I didn't
even mention uh rectal feeding which one
prisoner died because of the you know
the force trauma and they bled to death
through the rectum yeah no I mean this
this is torture and I can't believe the
US government calls it by a new name
just the euphan ism enhanced
interrogation there is no
difference and um so they they arrested
you again under the was it the Espionage
Act I'm sorry can you say that again I'm
sorry um did they arrest you under the
Espionage Act Yes actually I was charged
with three counts of Espionage um all as
a as a result of having a conversation
about torture with a reporter from The
New York Times and a reporter from ABC
News uh they charged me with Espionage
despite the fact that the reporter said
in the article that he wrote that uh he
had interviewed 24 current and former US
and foreign intelligence offic officers
for whatever reason the justice
department decided to go only after me
and you you had pointed out I believe it
was on Democracy Now that this is not a
case about um leaking leaking no it
never was it was right it was more about
just exposing the the torture yes the
the CIA never forgave me for exposing
the the torture program in 2007 and the
justice department began investigating
me just a few days later and that
investigation lasted until January of
2012 when I was finally charged with
with five
felonies and you you had also said that
uh people leak classified information
all the time and you mentioned uh names
like David
Petraeus
and um what was the other guy's name
manetta uh Leon Panetta was the director
of CIA before uh Petraeus was and so
right so it's they just basically like
make up the rules as they
go they they do and the truth of the
matter and I don't mean to make light of
of leaking but leaking is what makes
Washington operate people leak all the
time every single day and most of the
time those leaks are done on purpose
because they make whoever happens to be
in power uh look good uh they they make
it these leaks make it look like
presidents know what they're doing
secretaries of state are having
diplomatic successes and and of course
the US Military and intelligence
services are are running rough rough
shot over our enemies that's what those
leaks are for but when a leak doesn't
make the government good look good or
when a leak actively makes the
government look bad that's when they go
after the leaker the
truth the truth that's right that's what
makes them look bad this is the
truth um so to yeah talk a little bit um
about the prison conditions there there
there was one thing that you said um in
the uh interview with Amy Goodman that
you know I was like really cheering when
you said that about this bully
Lieutenant uh guard that was there and
said to you you better start acting like
an
inmate oh yeah I I went nose to nose
with a lieutenant one night
he had been he had been listening in on
a phone call that I had made to my wife
and uh I was recounting to her uh an
incident that I had seen in the in the
commissary earlier in the day in which a
corrections officer was was berading a
an inmate and he was swearing at him I
mean really ferociously swearing at him
and I said to my wife that I thought the
co was a nimrod so apparently I really
hurt this Lieutenant's delicate
sensibilities by using the word Nimrod
and uh he called me to the Lieutenant's
office quite late in the evening 9:20
we're locked in ourselves at 9:00 and
there's a 9:30 count and it's just uh
unheard of to miscount so I went down to
his office at 9:20 and um I got off on
the wrong foot because I when I walked
in he said to me uh are you an educated
man and I said said look I don't answer
rhetorical questions why don't you just
say what you want to say and that set
him off he was screaming at me he was
swearing at me and finally he shouted
you need to act more like an inmate and
that's when I sort of lost my temper and
I said and what is that supposed to mean
does that mean I should get a tattoo on
my face yeah does that mean I should
steal food from the cafeteria and sell
it around the uh the compound because if
it means that I should ring my hands and
say yes sir no sir thank you sir that's
never going to happen I have a question
for you John um so how do you think we
can reform the prison
system well one thing that I think we
need to do right off the bat is make it
a little tougher to get a job in an
American prison the only qualifications
that one need have to become a prison
guard is you have to have a GED and no
felony convictions and that's it I'm not
exaggerating when I say that I
encountered a half a dozen different
guards who literally couldn't read which
made mail call a
nightmare I I got one of your I read
your prison your prison letters and I
remember you complaining about
that yeah it got ugly a couple
times um so instead of hiring these
flunkies from the military who couldn't
cut it in the military and who couldn't
make it through the local police academy
and then as a job of Last Resort went to
the Bureau of Prisons we make we need to
make those jobs attractive we need to
make them we need to we need to provide
salaries that make them attractive to
people who actually have a choice in a
in a uh career make it make it something
to be proud of we also uh we need to
screen uh applicants uh we need to do
psychological screening because the Bop
really is a Dumping Ground for people
who probably have been bullied during
the course of their lifetimes and this
this has just eaten at them over the
years uh over the decades even and they
take it out on people who can't defend
themselves people who can't even talk
back because if you talk back to a
prison guard you're accused of insolence
and insolence gets you a one-way ticket
to solitary and we know what solitary is
like it's just like the Abus of family
system you know it's almost like um
there's like an epidemic of lowering the
bar instead of raising the bar and
expecting more from people because even
even uh the police officers I I believe
that they've actually I don't know about
in any other um state but I I in New
York I I think they've lowered the
criteria even for for NYPD because they
you know they want um I think they they
want people like that you know they want
people that that are just going to bully
and
abuse yeah because they think it's going
to keep people in line let me give you
one example too and I don't mean to sort
of devolve into anecdotes but I think
this is important I had been at Loretto
for about two weeks and I was working in
the uh prison library and I was just
sitting there and two Pennsylvania state
troopers walked in and they asked for
one of the COS one of the Corrections
Officers who was working there and right
there in front of everybody they
arrested him and they took him out and
they they didn't cuff him until they got
to the Lieutenant's office they didn't
want to cuff him in front of inmates uh
but it turned out that he was being
arrested for domestic violence he had
beaten his wife the day before and uh
and the next day he was right there at
his job again and I heard later that his
wife had dropped the charges no and so
because he hadn't been convicted of a
felony he was able to uh keep his job
but even in cases of domestic violence
if the if the victim drops the charges
like the the city or something can can
um still arrest that person because you
know right like they they they know that
the victim can have uh and be
intimidated I mean that that's the way
that it used to be that's that's true
but
in this case even if he had been
convicted it was only a
misdemeanor so there was no recourse for
anybody we were stuck with
him and so there was a uh was it a
congressman Moran who was sticking up
for you yeah Congressman Jim Moran a
Democrat from Virginia uh who's now
former Congressman Jim Moran he retired
uh last year very bravely went to the
floor of the House of Representatives in
November and called on the president to
pardon me so I hope that in the coming
year and a half or so I can build
Congressional support that it would
allow me to to apply for a a pardon and
have that application taken
seriously because right he he was on
your side and and I mean you know
obviously program sorry
uh you know you know he he sounds like a
completely rational person unlike um I
was just going to play just a little bit
a clip of the Neil the prosecutor Neil
McBride I mean who like this guy sounds
like you know he's a just a complete
perpetuation of the
propaganda so it's only going to take
maybe a half a
minute it's a welcome development that
kako can serve the rest of a cent at
home with his family she wrote meanwhile
the federal prosecutor in the case Neil
McBride has defended the government's
handling of the case he spoke after
kaku's sentencing in January of
2013 as the judge just said uh in
court today's sentence should be a
reminder to every individual who works
for the government who comes into the
possession of closely held sensitive
information regarding the national uh
defense or the identity of a covert
agent uh that it is critical that that
information uh remain secure and not
spill out uh into the public domain or
be shared with others who don't have
authorized access to it for more so yeah
I mean that guy is just completely
perpetuating the the
theater yeah and you notice he didn't
say anything about uh General Petraeus
who gave classified information to his
lover uh or to or about Leon Panetta uh
who left the CIA to become Secretary of
Defense who outed the name of the Navy
SEAL who killed Osama Bin Laden in a
room full of people that included
Hollywood producers uh or he didn't say
anything about General James cartright
who leaked information to the New York
Times about the stuck net virus and how
uh the US government initiated the the
stuck net virus in an attack against the
Iranian nuclear program he didn't say
anything about those leaks he focused on
just one leak one that didn't make the
government look good exactly that's what
they don't like the truth um can you
talk a little bit about um how the media
and the White House are kind
of in a
relationship well you know I always used
to chuckle at the notion that the
mainstream media was this corporate
media uh you know tied to the
Administration regardless of who was in
power and I absolutely believe that 100%
now uh the the mainstream media
especially the major networks uh just
simply do not follow uh whistleblower
stories they're just not concerned about
whistleblowers even n National Security
whistleblowers I I find that to be odd
the only the only coverage really is the
alternative press and I've gotten to the
Point myself where I watch Al jazer I
watch RT I watch democracy now and
otherwise I get all of my news from uh
from Twitter that's the only place where
I can really trust uh to get to get my
news you know sites like the intercept
for example fantastic website um but
yeah the the corporate media really is
in bed with with the white house because
if they aren't if they if they don't get
in bed with the White House they lose
their access and you know we've seen
this with the CIA over the years many
many times where where the cia's office
of public affairs will tell a journalist
if you publish that you're never welcome
here again we'll never talk to you again
and we'll never work with you on any
stories again and the White House does
exactly the same
thing I mean it it all just sounds so
illegitimate I mean like the whole thing
is just like completely illegitimate and
all these people and all their positions
of power
and it it just all looks so nice and
impressive or they try to make it look
that way but it's just it's a big
incestuous relationship is what it is
right just you know yeah like like
complete and utter codependency
and no nobody nobody being real and and
you know um holding you know I mean you
know because real relationships when you
really um you know care about somebody
you know you tell it to them like it
is I have a question for John yes sir um
so the President says we have Americans
have suffered from Terror and as a
result our government went to far yet um
he says we should not prosecute
torturers and those who ordered it but
look forward are we doomed that justice
has failed and history will will repeat
itself does that imply that treaties and
international law only apply if it is
convenient for propaganda oh I I think I
think that's exactly right um and one
thing that really disturbs me and I I
said this on Democracy Now um last week
is that we have not seen definitive
legislation that would ban torture in
perpetuity we have a policy decision in
the form of an executive order that says
we can't torture but that can change
with the very next election that's right
and what about the Geneva conventions
and what about the Geneva Convention
that's right that's right I'd like to
know how it is that our government can
justify
ignoring uh International treaties to
which we're
signatories that would protect people in
our custody from torture and that's all
we do is ignore it yeah yeah you're
right you're totally right we um we
brought up uh a bit in in the previous
um hour when uh Mr Benny was on you know
exactly sort of this point about you
know Obama when it comes to those that
participated in the torture program you
know and how he wants to look forward
and you know I just don't understand why
doesn't he have that attitude with um
you know the the the the jails in this
country that are overflowing with people
that do absolutely like non
crimes yeah you're you're exactly right
and one thing that really bothers me too
and I've said this in the past
reasonable people can agree to disagree
about whether or not right CIA officers
who believed they were acting lawfully
should be prosecuted I understand that
right but what about those CIA officers
that obviously broke the law that
obviously went over and above what had
been authorized by the justice
department what about the CIA officers
that killed Hassan ghoul in a cold cell
what about the CIA officers that used
that used hummus of all things to to
recy so-called hydrate uh a prisoner uh
why why aren't those CIA officers being
prosecuted where's the Justice there but
um that sort of uh is the point though
is that uh and I kind of think of you
know what what bill bny was talking
about with you know the the
um the like the pertinent information
instead of instead of making it easier
so that they can find the pertinent
information they want to make the H hay
stack bigger almost on purpose so that
you it makes the pertinent information
harder to find and so what you just said
right there about when things are
clear right instead of seeing what's
clear they want to bury what's clear
yeah there's always this
obfuscation they always going to bury it
right like they do the exact opposite of
what you know rational
sanity would do that's right what
healthy you know like you know rational
thinking
people I mean it's right it's like they
they want to obscure
reality they do this is this is actually
part of a wellth thought out plan and
this is why we saw so many former CIA
officers on on TV in the immediate
aftermath of the release of the torture
report just bloviating on about how it
worked and it was important than it was
legal because this is their
legacy when their obituaries are
written it they're going to say that
that these men were instrumental in the
creation and the implementation of the
torture program and what they have to do
to save their own legacies is to repeat
this lie over and over and over again
that torture worked and hope that the
American people finally believe it so
that's the hay stack is the lie and the
repetition of the lie that's like the
verbal you know um you know I'm trying
to think of 1984 and George Orwell um
mind speak what's that well and that's
the way uh propaganda works and
brainwashing is repetition it usually
takes three statements before it sinks
into the average person's uh mind but uh
yeah if you repeat a lie and I forgot
who was famous that that said that uh I
think he was one of Hitler's propaganda
ministers uh eventually the public will
uh uh accept that as
history so um yeah that that's basically
like how they keep the people confused
and of course if the public is not um
countering that you know it's like you
have
to uh exercise you know your connection
to reality or if someone is going to be
constantly feeding you a lie then
they're going to be able to sort of you
know knock people off of their feet and
and um the people are going to lose
their grip basically to what is
real and and what
is you know lies in propaganda I I have
a question for John and and that is if
you could name
names who would you say General Hayden
uh di
chinii what do you think in terms of
prosecution yeah you know in terms of
who ordered this and who should be
prosecuted yeah yeah who ordered it I
think this was really this was really
Dick Cheney's program yeah while while
President Bush
signature uh is on the orders this sure
but we know he didn't really know what
was going on that's right that's right
yeah I I would I would put it on
Cheney um I guess we we should just
mention uh Diane Feinstein who you you
were surprised that she actually um
was um not in favor of you know when
when it came out in the details of uh
how much worse that people thought that
it was
right Diane Feinstein really has been a
cheerleader for for the CIA for many
many years and she was she was known as
being an unusually friendly uh
chairwoman of the Senate select
committee on intelligence so for her to
come out uh with with the the
ferociousness that she did not just
because of what U what we learned from
the report but because of the cia's
behavior toward the Senate Select
committee's
Staff uh breaking into the computers for
example uh
withdrawing cable traffic for for her to
come out and publicly take the agency to
task that was a very big deal and and
you could tell she she was really upset
that just wasn't for the cameras and so
um I guess a question could be uh
I mean she's
obviously you know feels free enough to
speak out in challenge of that I mean
she's not she has the authority to do
something about it oh so I mean may may
would she be just someone that that
would be good to go to perhaps to get
people prosecuted I mean can she do that
I don't think that she ever would I I
don't think that she supports
prosecutions she um she certainly hasn't
in the past she really is a very
strongly pro-- CIA Senator I think she
was personally offended that the CIA
disrespected her by breaking into the
staff's computers oh so it was more like
a personal thing I think it was oh
well that just lets some of the air out
of my to but with that said with that
said there's there's a a a senator on
the ssci Senator Ron weiden a Democrat
of Oregon who really is very courageous
in his willingness to to stand up to the
agency and to um truly exert oversight
something that other Senators just
aren't willing to to do if the Democrats
win control of the Senate again it'll be
Ron weiden who becomes the chairman of
that committee and I think things will
be different well let me let me tell you
about my personal experience with the
political scene I I went with the uh
former head of the LA FBI gave testimony
in front of 20 three Senators uh the
Judiciary Committee and the Senate
intelligence committee you know under
closed doors and and uh you know all our
cell phones had to be taken away and
stuff and uh you know the the stuff that
I study MK Ultra and uh you know some of
these secret programs brainwashing and
and behavior modification they had never
heard of MK Ultra and we just looked at
each other and I was like and you're in
charge
of overseeing the intelligence
committees what's wrong with you people
so I I'm just sharing one of my
experiences see that's that really that
really makes it clear doesn't it yeah it
does it it makes it clear and then all
the you know there were several Senators
who were interested in what we were
talking about to try to pass bills or
what it might whatever it may be and uh
they were voted out within four you know
two years and and so by the time you
develop any sort of relationship with
these Senators uh they're they're
switching and you can't get anything
done so I understand why America is
where it
is um I just um you um John had said
that no one was trained to be an
interrogator that they actually were
walking up and down the hallways in the
CIA like trying to recruit staff to be
an interrogator yeah yeah that's true
there was no professional interrogator
Cadre at the CIA and so and so they
would just you know take whoever and
without any
training right and just send them
overseas and they were on their own wow
all right well I heard differently I
heard there was an interrogation school
that Dick Cheney set up uh way back in
2002 uh I was there in 2002 there wasn't
anything like that there wasn't okay all
right I'm I'm wrong uh you you also um
spoke about um a Washington Post article
in
1971 yes where they uh
indicted a us more than that there was a
there was a picture on the front page of
the Washington Post in January of 1971
that showed an American Soldier
waterboarding a North Vietnamese
prisoner yeah and when that photo was
published
the Pentagon ordered an
investigation they Court marshalled the
soldier uh and then they they tried him
for torture and they convicted him and
he actually went to went to prison to a
military prison for torturing that
prisoner and and I asked
rhetorically why was torture illegal in
1971 but not illegal in
2002 right what changed nothing should
have changed right
they I think their overreach is so much
worse today that like their their level
of arrogance is spilling over today yes
I agree um so I and you actually don't
believe that Edward Snowden should ever
come back to the United States I don't
think that Ed Snowden would get a fair
trial in the United States especially in
the eastern district of Virginia which
is where you know the government shops
around these cases and they try to bring
charges uh in the eastern district of
Virginia as frequently as they can
that's where I was charged that's where
um Julian Assange has been uh has been
investigated that's where Ed snowden's
charges have been uh leveled and uh
Jeffree Sterling was uh was tried and
convicted in the eastern district of
Virginia right Jeffrey Sterling um can
we talk just a little bit about Stephen
Kim sure uh thought that was a pretty
interesting uh story just you know
recently they they put this guy um in
jail who who it seemed like he was
clearly framed because it was the state
department that actually introduced him
to the um the
[Music]
media right yeah Stephen Kim is is an
example of how
things can go to pot it's like being
like he was just trapped like he they
trapped him and you can do nothing to
save yourself it it's a
nightmare what happened to Stephen
Kim see I'm sorry say that again it was
a nightmare what happened to Stephen Kim
and he could do nothing to save himself
because once they make a decision that
they're gonna go after you you're going
to go to prison right prop publica came
out with a report a couple of years ago
that said that
98.2% of all federal cases result in a
conviction
98.2 now I I made a comment at the time
that Saddam Hussein won 98% uh in his
last presidential race and we said it
was fixed but the justice department
wins 98% of their cases and we say
they're Geniuses right it seems to me
that something's wrong there
right uh you know it's it's it's
completely rigged I mean the system is
just obviously completely rigged there's
no law that anybody is abiding by
there's no rules that the those in
charge are adhering to they they hold uh
you know people to to just you know
whatever set of rules they just feel
like making up and then hold no rules to
themselves and their friends I mean it's
just a
complete you know
breakdown it is it is there there are
different rules for different people and
that's the sad truth about about
Washington so
what what is your solution joh like what
do you think people have to do well I
think the first thing we should do is
rewrite the Espionage Act the Espionage
Act was written in
1917 and it was targeted against German
sabur during World War I it was slightly
updated in 1950 after the execution of
Julius and Ethel Rosenberg but the the
law is so Antiquated that it doesn't
even mention classified information the
classification system hadn't yet been
invented it mentions only National
Defense information and it's so broad
that virtually anybody with access to
classified information can be charged
with Espionage even if if the leak is
accidental even if the leak resulted in
in no uh uh harm to the National
Security and the first thing we need to
do is rewrite the ESPN act what about um
the like they the fact that they're just
abusing the Espionage Act oh yeah I I
said in the Guardian A couple of years
ago that that the administration uses
the Espionage Act as an iron fist yeah
with which they can smash people who
disagree publicly with the
administration's policies because it's
also they they abuse the word classified
also it's it's you know the term
classified doesn't really mean
classified it means you know covering up
their criminal Behavior and the
Espionage Act doesn't really mean the
Espionage Act it's it's all just
whatever again like whatever they want
it to mean yeah it has nothing to do
with Espionage anymore and I'll tell you
another thing about classification um
there are billions of classified
documents that are created each year uh
and what PE what most people don't know
is that over classification is a crime
there's actually law that prohibits the
over classification of information uh in
the intelligence Community but the law
is utterly ignored and certainly no one
has ever been prosecuted for over
classifying anything we only have two
minutes left but you know again what you
just said goes back to making the hay
stack bigger so that you can't find the
pertinent information like they they're
constantly trying to bury the truth
that's absolutely true it it becomes a
quagmire um so John kyaku you don't have
a website I mean people can follow you
on Twitter though right uh I do have a
website um it's it's being revamped but
uh but you can check it out at
www.de joh.com and I'm also on Twitter
at John kiraku and you're on Facebook
and I'm on Facebook why not Dr Robert
Duncan did you want
um say we have a minute oh yeah well I
just wanted to thank John for his uh
work that he's done to bring torture
forward and and uh I know he's paid a
very heavy price for what he's done but
it's for the good of the United States
and it's for the good of the human
people and uh so I I just want to thank
you again for doing what you've done for
us thank you very much that's very kind
of you so that does it for this Tuesday
February 24th uh organic news here on
awake radio uh please friend me on
Facebook even though I know I think
Facebook is something like we should all
get off of because NSA is just spying on
all of us um my YouTube channel is
April Waters with two teas uh donations
are greatly appreciated to support
Independent Media so thank you and I
hope to meet you guys both in person
someday look forward to that thanks
thank you have a great night thank you
good night
[Music]
you
i' stood upon my mountain top and shed
at
the walked above the pement with my
senses
Amplified I get this
feeling on my news a ni just tend to the
touch sometimes super sensitive but you
can get too
much I get
this changes Mak
s
got
ches
emotion behind
it sometimes they coming out like
shadows in the
dark I get this
feeling when I think about all I miss
And all I'll never
seen when I think about the people who
have opened up to
me I
[Music]
this changes make sense
again I'm the
ch
[Music]
snow fall deep around my house and holds
a
winter I've heard the lions hunting in
the
S
night I get
this Forest factories and Riv sea and
sky hungry child in the
desert and the fly as Cloud her
eyes I get
this my changes T oh yeah the
pleas my
Chang
again
I'm
yeah pleasure leaves a fingerprint
surely is more than
pain in memories they resonate I they go
back again
[Music]
CH
hello
[Music]
yeah
it just takes a minute and you feel no
pain got to make something of your life
give me one more pain you come to see
the doctor cuz I'll show you the Cure
I'm going to take away the questions
yeah I'm going to make you
show
yeah a h man for the order ever when you
come go to school had a skin job for
hand you yeah you looks pretty cool how
a have the
main the
Dragon no regret you got no go nothing
more now I know
you because we got so much to
do
you got nothing more to
do so take
this to
operation the ground reolution work
know
sh there a j for you in the system
boy w
w
hey [__] you know everything gotor is to
do is's a gun sh it home with my phone
we stand someone over to bring you what
you need to one man death machine make
this steady bed know you to do I know
you got so to do we got to
much
[Music]
take the ground Revolution
working the ground
I a job for you in a system boy
nothing
now let me into your
mind
all